[
  {
    "question": "Which mammal is known to have the most powerful bite in the world?",
    "answer": "hippopotamus",
    "id": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What object does a male penguin often gift to a female penguin to win her over?",
    "answer": "a pebble",
    "id": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "A dog sweats through which part of its body?",
    "answer": "its paws",
    "id": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the size of a newborn kangaroo?",
    "answer": "one inch",
    "id": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal is known to spend 90% of its day sleeping?",
    "answer": "koalas",
    "id": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is the tongue of a giraffe?",
    "answer": "purple",
    "id": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal’s stripes are on their skin as well as their fur?",
    "answer": "tiger",
    "id": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal’s poop is known to take the shape of cubes?",
    "answer": "wombat",
    "id": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "Under their white fur, what color is a polar bear’s skin?",
    "answer": "black",
    "id": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "How many compartments are in a cow’s stomach?",
    "answer": "four",
    "id": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "How long does it take a sloth to digest a meal?",
    "answer": "two weeks",
    "id": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the fastest land animal?",
    "answer": "cheetah",
    "id": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "A baby goat is called what?",
    "answer": "kid",
    "id": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the only mammal that’s able to fly?",
    "answer": "bat",
    "id": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s a group of kittens called?",
    "answer": "four",
    "id": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "How many compartments are in a cow’s stomach?",
    "answer": "kindle",
    "id": 16
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the horns of a rhinoceros made of?",
    "answer": "hair",
    "id": 17
  },
  {
    "question": "How many compartments are in a cow’s stomach?",
    "answer": "four",
    "id": 18
  },
  {
    "question": "How many humps does a Bactrian camel have?",
    "answer": "two",
    "id": 19
  },
  {
    "question": "What name is given to a female deer?",
    "answer": "doe",
    "id": 20
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal is said to have nine lives?",
    "answer": "cat",
    "id": 21
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal is known by the nickname 'sea cow'?",
    "answer": "manatee",
    "id": 22
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
    "answer": "elephant",
    "id": 23
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal is the largest mammal in the world?",
    "answer": "blue whale",
    "id": 24
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal eats mainly bamboo?",
    "answer": "elephant",
    "id": 25
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
    "answer": "panda",
    "id": 26
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal is known to be 'man’s best friend'?",
    "answer": "dog",
    "id": 27
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal can stand on its tail?",
    "answer": "kangaroo",
    "id": 28
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal is the tallest in the world??",
    "answer": "giraffe",
    "id": 29
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal is covered in quills?",
    "answer": "porcupine",
    "id": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of turtle can’t retract into its shell?",
    "answer": "sea turtle",
    "id": 31
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of animal is a Komodo dragon?",
    "answer": "a lizard",
    "id": 32
  },
  {
    "question": "What does a snake shed a few times a year?",
    "answer": "its skin",
    "id": 33
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal can move its eyes independently?",
    "answer": "a chameleon",
    "id": 34
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal breathes out of its butt?",
    "answer": "turtles",
    "id": 35
  },
  {
    "question": "How many layers of skin does a chameleon have?",
    "answer": "four",
    "id": 36
  },
  {
    "question": "What do snakes use to smell?",
    "answer": "their tongue",
    "id": 37
  },
  {
    "question": "The King Cobra is also called what?",
    "answer": "the hamadryad",
    "id": 38
  },
  {
    "question": "What feature is visibly different between alligators and crocodiles?",
    "answer": "their snout",
    "id": 39
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the name of the largest snake in the world?",
    "answer": "anaconda",
    "id": 40
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of reptiles are leatherbacks and ridleys?",
    "answer": "turtles",
    "id": 41
  },
  {
    "question": "What reptile is known for the ability to change its body color?",
    "answer": "chameleon",
    "id": 42
  },
  {
    "question": "What reptile is known for the ability to change its body color?",
    "answer": "lizard",
    "id": 43
  },
  {
    "question": "The larvae stage of a frog is called what?",
    "answer": "tadpole",
    "id": 44
  },
  {
    "question": "Do frogs lay eggs?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "id": 45
  },
  {
    "question": "Which amphibian has a tail?",
    "answer": "salamanders",
    "id": 46
  },
  {
    "question": "How many groups of amphibians are there?",
    "answer": "three",
    "id": 47
  },
  {
    "question": "A wart-covered amphibian with leathery skin is a what?",
    "answer": "toad",
    "id": 48
  },
  {
    "question": "Are frogs more active during the day or at night?",
    "answer": "at night",
    "id": 49
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you call a frog’s ears?",
    "answer": "tympanums",
    "id": 50
  },
  {
    "question": "Which butterfly migrates?",
    "answer": "monarchs",
    "id": 51
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is an Elephant Hawk-Moth?",
    "answer": "pink",
    "id": 52
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the largest group of insects?",
    "answer": "beetles",
    "id": 53
  },
  {
    "question": "How many legs do cockroaches have?",
    "answer": "six",
    "id": 54
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s a newly hatched butterfly called?",
    "answer": "caterpillar",
    "id": 55
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the loudest insect in the world?",
    "answer": "cicada",
    "id": 56
  },
  {
    "question": "What insect was the first living creature to be sent into space?",
    "answer": "fruit fly",
    "id": 57
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the smallest known insect?",
    "answer": "fairyfly",
    "id": 58
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ant has the most painful sting?",
    "answer": "bullet ant",
    "id": 59
  },
  {
    "question": "How many stages of metamorphosis do most insects go through?",
    "answer": "four",
    "id": 60
  },
  {
    "question": "What part of its body does a butterfly taste with?",
    "answer": "its feet",
    "id": 61
  },
  {
    "question": "How many flowers do honey bees have to visit in order to make one pound of honey?",
    "answer": "two million",
    "id": 62
  },
  {
    "question": "How many eyes do caterpillars have?",
    "answer": "twelve",
    "id": 63
  }
]